[ car traveling ]
- [ suspension squeaking ] - [ wind whooshing ]
[ suspenseful music plays ]
[ more intense music plays ]
- [ crickets chirp ] - [ car slows down ]
[ car doors open ]
[ car doors shut ]
[ suspenseful music ]
[ random chatter , singing and laughter ]
[ splash ]
I 'm sorry . Is this chair free ?
Yeah , um ... sure .
[ Patrick ] Thank you so much .
You 're welcome .
[ speaking foreign language ]
- [ splash ] - [ Patrick ] Ah , whoo !
[ speaking in foreign language ]
[ mother and child speaking in foreign language ]
And please don 't give her any apple juice before bedtime .
Apple juice , yes , yes . Like the other night .
Yeah , but no apple juice .
Yeah , it 's too much sugar .
Okay , no .
- Hi-hi . - Hi , Ma .
- Ciao . - Ciao .
[ both speaking in foreign language ] ... cooking class .
[ random chatter , cutlery clattering ]
[ Derek ] Today we made ravioli with um ,
I think there were bits of sausages inside it .
Well , you should come to the cooking class with us
maybe tomorrow ,
because I believe that tomorrow they 're making the gnocchi .
The ravioli that they tried to teach ...
- [ clinking glasses for toast ] - [ Derek ] Oh , right .
I 'm sorry to bother you during this very lovely dinner .
I just want to say two things . I hope we didn 't wake you up ,
because the noise you heard last night , the banging on the door ,
- [ all laugh ] - Very quickly , that was me .
- [ laughter ] - We couldn 't find our way ,
so we were very late here .
Ah-ah , sorry for that .
Ah , we don 't know each other .
That 's the way it goes on holidays .
But uh , you know , I want to meet you people ,
because you look all so nice and beautiful .
And uh , I want to toast to you , guys . To Italy , of course .
To the food , of course . And to love .
[ all toast ] Too love , salute !
- [ glasses clinking ] - [ random chatter ]
♪
[ singing ]
[ singing continues ]
[ crickets chirping ]
[ church bells ringing ]
[ dog barking ]
[ motorcycle passing , street chatter ]
Like a bunny ... for kids ?
Nah ? Okay , well . Ciao .
[ man on bench ] Ciao .
[ baby crying , man laughs , chatter ]
[ choir sings in background ]
[ Patrick ] It goes up and down , and up and down ...
[ Louise laughing ] It 's so hot , yeah . But you do it ...
[ Bjørn speaking foreign language ]
[ Louise ] Hi ! This is my husband , Bjørn .
Patrick , nice to meet you .
We met at the Villa ?
- [ Patrick ] Right . - [ Bjørn laughs ]
- [ Bjørn ] Hi . - Hi . Karin .
Sorry , I forgot to introduce myself . I 'm Louise ...
- [ Patrick ] Hello . - And this is Agnes .
And what 's your name ?
[ Louise speaking foreign language ]
Abel has difficulties speaking .
So , if he feels some sort of pressure
he can get a little insecure .
- [ both ] Ahh . - But there 's no pressure at all .
And who is this ?
[ speaking foreign language ]
[ Agnes ] Ninus .
Ninus ?
Agnes just lost it , so Bjørn went to find it .
You went to find the rabbit ?
[ Bjørn ] Yes .
That 's very heroic of you .
[ laughs ] Thank you .
No , no . I 'm serious ... respect .
Well , thanks .
You 're very welcome .
So , did you guys have lunch yet ?
[ Louise ] By the way , where are you guys from ?
[ Karin ] Holland , the southern part .
Yeah , countryside , it 's a beautiful area .
Wow , I would just love to move outside the city
and be close to nature and all ... Yeah .
Well , you should come and visit us .
- That would be great ... - [ waiter ] Lasagna Vegeteriana .
- [ waiter ] Prego . - Ci , Vegetarian ?
- [ waiter ] Vegetarian . - Yes , thank you .
- [ waiter ] Tagliatelle ai funghi . - Ci , grazia .
[ waiter ] E pizza margherita .
So , you 're a vegetarian ?
Yeah , I eat fish , but yes , I 'm a vegetarian .
That 's so good . We could all learn from you .
Yeah , good for the environment , really .
Well ... thank you ...
[ waiter ] E peposo .
Oh , Grazie Mille . Oh , I 'm starving .
- It looks good . - [ Patrick ] Looks great .
[ both laugh ]
[ Patrick ] Wow .
Well , I actually think that Dutch and Danish people
are very similar .
Yeah , so we 're the same . [ laughs ]
Well , in many ways I think so , actually .
It 's uh , the same humor ,
the same um , the same um ... same culture .
Yeah , at least we have more in common with people from Holland ,
than with the Swedish people .
[ Patrick ] I 's so glad you say that .
- Yeah ? - [ Bjørn laughs ]
Really . No , I had a Swedish colleague
when I worked for the Médecins Sans Frontières .
You 're a doctor ?
Yeah .
No , really . He was the most boring and political correct man
I 've ever met in my entire life .
- [ Bjørn chuckles ] - [ Patrick ] Really .
- [ polka music playing ] - [ children playing and laughing ]
[ random restaurant chatter ]
[ Bjørn ] ... you know saying weird stuff !
Like once we were in Greece , I was going with the cheering .
I was going ... " Kalimera ! "
[ Patrick ] Good morning !
[ speaking foreign language ]
[ mellow jazz plays in background ]
" Dear Louise , Bjørn and Agnes . How are you ?
We were just talking the other day
how nice it was spending time with you this summer .
And even though it 's been a while ,
we would love to invite you to come to visit us .
- What do you say ? " - [ both laugh ]
" A weekend in the Dutch countryside .
Food , wine and long walks .
And , oh , by the way , Abel keeps mentioning Agnes . So funny .
He really misses her .
All the best from Abel , Patrick and Karin . "
[ exhales ]
[ suspenseful music plays ]
[ suspenseful music continues ]
[ music becomes more tense ]
[ music stops ]
[ suspenseful music plays ]
[ suspenseful music continues ]
[ music ends ]
[ Karin ] Yeah , you made it !
[ Bjørn laughing ] Finally , yes .
[ Karin ] Yes , yes !
- [ Karin ] Hey . - [ Louise ] Hi .
[ Overlapping greetings , laughter ]
[ Karin ] So nice to see you again .
[ Patrick ] Hey , man .
[ Louise ] What a beautiful place .
[ Karin ] Thank you .
[ laughing ] Oh no , you can leave them on . Or take them off .
Leave them on .
Or take them off .
Leaving ' em on , taking ' em off , whatever you want .
- Thank you . - [ both giggle ]
- Give me your coat . - Thank you .
[ Karin ] Sorry for the mess .
[ Louise ] Oh , it 's nothing .
It 's gonna get much worse . Come on !
So , come in .
Wow , very comfortable .
Yeah , that 's the way we like it .
Oh , and we brought you something .
[ Karin ] Oh !
It 's a little souvenir from Denmark .
[ Bjørn ] It 's Louise who bought it , so ...
Thank you .
[ Karin ] Uh , where 's Abel ?
- Uh , downstairs maybe ? - Oh .
He 's been cooking all day . He 's making Wild Boar .
- [ Bjørn ] Wow ! - [ Patrick laughs ]
[ Karin ] Come on . This is your room .
- Wow . - Ah , that 's wonderful .
[ Karin speaking foreign language ]
- [ Patrick ] Bjørn ? - Yes .
- You want a beer ? - [ Bjørn ] Yeah .
I want to show you my pool .
- You have a pool ? - [ Patrick ] Uh-huh .
[ Karin speaking foreign language ]
Hi Abel .
Look , Agnes , we made you a little bed .
- [ Karin ] Do you like it ? - Yes , she likes it .
- [ TV in foreign language ] - [ speaking foreign language ]
[ Karin ] I forgot the presents . I 'm so sorry .
[ Louise ] No , it 's fine .
[ television in foreign language ]
Wow ... it 's coffee cups . That 's sweet .
- Yeah ? - Yeah .
And ... a mermaid ?
Yes , it 's something that I think represents Denmark very well .
- It 's The Little Mermaid . - Yeah .
I know it .
I 've heard it 's quite small and disappointing .
[ all chuckle ]
Well , actually there are some anecdotes about it
that are really nice .
Oh yeah , you know what is also nice ?
- Louise ... - Hmm ?
This is for you .
Oh , no-no , that 's fine ...
I insist .
- [ Louise laughs ] - I insist .
[ laughs ] No-no , I 'll wait till ...
- It 's my favorite part . - Okay .
It 's delicious . It 's crispy and soft at the same time .
- Yes . - [ speaking foreign language ]
Yeah .
- Hmm . - It 's good , right ?
Very good .
Oh , hi Abel .
[ wind rustling in background ]
[ knocking sound ]
[ Patrick speaking foreign language ]
[ Abel running ]
But it is really lucky we 've got the GPS ,
because otherwise we 'd have got lost like 20 times
I had it under control .
No , [ laughing ] the GPS had .
- I had . - [ both chuckle ]
[ Abel crying in background ]
It 's frightening sometimes ,
how we lose our ability to find our way through life .
Because we hand over the responsibility to technology .
That is so true .
I mean , people nowadays don 't have a clue how to read a map .
I must admit that driving in a car like that ,
with GPS and all these modern things , you ...
I-I want to turn it off sometimes .
And , as you were saying , Patrick ...
Is he all right ?
No , no , he 's fine . He 's fine . He 'll fall asleep in a minute .
He just does this sometimes . It 's part of his disease .
Oh yeah , what is that ?
Abel has what you call " congenital aglossia " .
Meaning basically , he 's born without a tongue .
Or ... a much smaller tongue than you and me .
But is he in pain ?
Oh no , no pain .
He just has a hard time making himself understandable .
Oh no , I understand everything he says .
[ Abel crying in background ]
- [ flicks lighter ] - [ door squeaks open ]
[ door squeaks shut ]
[ tense music swells ]
[ adults speaking in foreign language ]
[ Louise ] Excuse me for just one second .
Um , Abel , do you think you could move away ?
Uh , because Agnes really wants to try it .
[ adults speaking in foreign language ]
Uh , excuse me ?
Agnes really wants to try the slide .
And do you think it is possible
to ask Abel to move away just for one second ?
[ Karin ] So sorry about this .
No , it 's okay , it 's nothing .
[ Patrick speaking to Abel in foreign language ]
Patrick , it 's all right . He doesn 't have to .
No , he wants to say " I apologize " .
[ Karin ] Yeah , he really wants to .
[ Patrick speaks in foreign language ]
[ Abel ] Sorry .
[ Agnes sliding ]
[ Patrick speaks in foreign language ]
- I must have the recipe . - It 's good , right ?
It reminds me of what we call a Mazarin ?
A Mazarin tart ... a Danish thing .
Come here .
[ sighs ]
Hey , am I interrupting ?
No-no , of course not .
Well Patrick and I would like to invite you to dinner tonight .
Oh , that 's so nice of you .
Yeah , there 's a nice restaurant with great local food
just up the road .
And we wouldn 't want you to miss the opportunity
while you 're here .
That sounds good .
[ Karin ] Great .
[ bell rings ]
Yes , perfect timing .
[ conversation in foreign language ]
[ door shuts ]
[ Karin ] He doesn 't speak any English .
And who is Muhajid ?
[ Karin ] He 's the babysitter .
- The babysitter ? - [ Karin ] Yeah .
[ conversation foreign language ]
But the kids are going as well , right ?
No , tonight is without kids . Didn 't I tell you that ?
[ conversation foreign language ]
Muhajid is so very good with children .
The whole neighborhood uses him and not only because he 's cheap .
[ Agnes laughing ]
[ door shuts ]
- [ Patrick ] Hey guys ! - [ beeps horn ]
[ Patrick ] Let 's go !
[ Agnes giggling ]
[ Patrick ] Come on , let 's move .
- [ both laugh ] - [ car beeps horn ]
[ Patrick speaking foreign language ]
[ car engine rumbling ]
[ conversation in foreign language ]
[ conversation continues ]
Patrick , are we at the restaurant soon ?
We 'll be there in a minute .
Uh , What is the " stamp pot " ?
Oh , that 's great . It 's the house specialty ... you should try it ,
- Okay - It 's good .
Yeah , and the " boerenkool " ?
Boerenkool . Oh , that 's also stamp pot , you 'll love it .
It 's delicious , they make it very well here .
And what is stamp pot ?
Stamppot ? Oh , that 's typical Dutch . Very traditional .
Like potatoes and vegetables , you stamp it all together .
Steef ! Let me take care of you guys . Okay ?
Yeah , fine with me .
[ speaking foreign language ]
And remember , I 'm a vegetarian .
I 'm sorry ?
Yes , I don 't eat meat .
Oh , yes , yes . So good for the environment , yes .
But you eat fish , right ?
Yes .
So you 're not a vegetarian , you 're a pescatarian .
Yes , Steef ?
[ Steef and Patrick speaking foreign language ]
Hmm ?
And fish is not meat ?
Of course , um , but it 's better for the environment .
And the way the fishing industry works
and how we treat the oceans is not affecting the climate ?
[ scoffs ]
Well , I would like to propose a toast ...
- Okay . - For uh ,
- good times . - For good times .
- [ all toast ] - We say proost .
- Proost . - Proost .
- [ toasting ] Proost . - [ toasting ] Proost .
[ Bjørn chuckles ]
[ " Saturday Night " by Herman Brood plays ]
[ chuckling ]
[ Bjørn ] Well , I just hate this ...
[ all laughing ]
This , um , this team building bullshit , you know .
[ speaking foreign language ]
[ music continues ]
♪ Was just in time replaced By the magic appearance ♪
Of a new day while ♪
♪ A melancholic Reno was crawling on his back just in ♪
♪ Front of The supermarket doorway ♪
[ both laughing ]
♪ On a cold summer night as we stood on the corner ♪
♪ As a man passed by and asked us what we were doing ♪
What we need ♪
[ laughs ]
♪ As he pointed His big fat finger ♪
♪ To the people hangin ' round ♪
♪ At the corner Of the other side of street ♪
Oh well ♪
♪ Doin ' nothing , just hanging around ... ♪
♪ Doin ' nothing , just hanging around ♪
♪ His head all busted lookin ' just a little too wise child ♪
I just can 't wait ♪
For Saturday night ♪
Saturday night ♪
[ Karin and Patrick breathing heavy , groaning ]
Saturday night . ♪
Wow .
Someone had a really good time tonight .
You want us to chip in ?
Oh , thanks man .
[ Bjørn scoffs ]
So the dinner is on us ?
Oh , that 's so kind . Thanks , man , thanks .
[ slaps arm ]
- [ speaking foreign language ] - [ Bjørn sighs ]
[ car rumbling ]
Ah .
[ tires screeching ]
[ speaking foreign language ]
[ rock music plays ]
[ turns up volume ]
Patrick , can you turn down the music a bit ?
Patrick , the music , can you turn it down ...
I love this song . This is a great song !
Turn down the fucking music .
[ Karin laughs ]
Listen to it !
[ speaking foreign language ]
[ turns off music ]
I 'm so sorry , he 's just so drunk . I 'm truly sorry . Okay ?
[ speaking foreign language ]
[ Patrick ] I truly apologize , I 'm so sorry .
And ya ! [ turns loud music back on ]
[ Karin and Patrick laugh , jeer ]
- Patrick ! - Just a little bit , please ?
Just a little bit down .
- [ Patrick ] Just a little bit . - [ Karin laughs ]
[ loud music plays ]
- [ Patrick ] Okay , a little bit . - Yeah !
[ Patrick turns music down ]
Yeah . Thank you .
[ car rumbling , tires screeching ]
[ Louise sighs , clears throat ]
[ shower running ]
[ door squeaks open ]
[ door shuts ]
[ footsteps ]
[ turns tap on , brushes teeth ]
[ brushing continues ]
[ footsteps ]
- [ rinses mouth , spits ] - [ door shuts ]
[ faucet squeaks , shuts water off ]
[ quivering ]
[ door squeaks open and shut ]
[ kissing ]
- [ kiss ] - [ Louise moans ]
[ heavy breathing , kissing ]
[ breathing heavier ]
[ breathing heavy ]
[ door squeaks open ]
[ Agnes groans ]
[ door squeaks shut ]
Bjørn , Bjorn , Bjørn , Bjorn !
Bjørn .
[ door squeaks shut ]
[ footsteps ]
[ car horn beeps , door opens ]
[ door shuts ]
[ car starts ]
[ car drives off ]
[ birds squawk ]
[ opens trunk ]
[ fidgeting with luggage ]
[ shuts trunk ]
[ birds squawk ]
[ Agnes sniffling ]
[ eerie music plays ]
[ music stops ]
[ opens door ]
[ footsteps ]
We had some really lovely days here .
- Huh ? - [ Karin ] What 's going on ?
Well , uh , we have a situation here .
Someone left without saying goodbye .
No , as I was just trying to tell Patrick ,
we had some really lovely days .
And then I ask again , why are you leaving ...
[ Karin interrupts in foreign language ]
We had some good days , it 's just um ...
there 's just some things that ...
that make us believe that it 's best that we go home .
What are those things ? I want to know .
- It 's um , many things . - Such as ?
It 's just , um ... such as ...
Such as the bed for instance . It 's really small , and uh ,
and Agnes doesn 't want to sleep on the floor ,
so she comes in at night .
Okay , so with all of your respect ...
First of all , I 'm a vegetarian .
But all you 've been doing since we got here was serving meat .
But we have all sorts of food . You can have a hagelslag
sandwich right now . I can make it for you .
No , thank you .
And last night at that restaurant or ...
roadhouse or whatever that place was , it was ...
it was very uncomfortable to drive .
And the music was so loud .
And you were drinking and driving .
And the way you were touching each other in front of us
that just made me so uncomfortable , I 'm really sorry .
But it just um ... so many things have felt so wrong .
I 'm really sorry , but it 's just how it is .
I 'm in shock .
[ opens refrigerator , clangs bottles ]
[ shuts fridge ]
Can-can I say something ?
Uh , first of all ... Louise .
I am so sorry that we forgot that you were a vegetarian .
And if there are things you don 't eat ,
you just could have told us .
Right ?
[ Louise scoffs ]
And our house is not huge ,
so we cannot offer you a big luxury room
and a king-size bed , Bjørn . I 'm sorry .
And I am truly sorry that Agnes doesn 't feel comfortable
staying in Abel 's room . But we thought it was only natural .
I mean , if you only knew how much Abel was looking forward to
sharing his toys in his room with Agnes .
And the roadhouse , as you call it ...
the hugging and the dancing .
We were just having a fun evening . Guys , come on .
I mean , dancing and kissing the one you love .
What 's the problem ?
To me , it 's crossing the line
when you pick up my daughter at night .
And then you take her into your bed ,
where you slept next to her , naked .
Yeah but , where were you ?
Louise , I mean , Agnes kept calling ?
She was crying .
[ Karin ] Where were you ?
First of all there 's nothing we can do now to change the way
you have felt during these past few days .
And it truly breaks my heart to hear
that you haven 't enjoyed your stay .
It makes me wonder if maybe I 've failed as a host .
No one is forcing you to stay .
But I really hope you do , ' cause today is gonna be a great day .
I promise you , today , it 's gonna be great .
[ Karin scoffs ]
[ Louise clears throat ]
[ Abel and Agnes kicking ball ]
[ suspenseful music ]
[ speaking foreign language ]
It 's this scissor . It doesn 't cut anything , it 's so dull .
[ Louise raking ]
[ eerie music plays ]
[ car rumbles ]
This is okay if I turn on the radio ?
Yeah , of course .
You can turn it up if you like .
[ radio plays in background ]
So , what kind of music do you like ?
Ah , well ...
yeah , I listen to , you know , all kinds .
Like uh ... like pop and rock and , uh ...
yeah , basically all kinds you know .
- And you ? - Me too .
Pop , rock ... funk .
Hmm .
I like music that I can sing along to . I like singing .
- Yeah , singing is good . - Yeah .
Actually , there 's a lot of great Dutch music .
You want me to play you some ?
Yeah yeah , please . I 'd really like to hear some .
- You sure ? - Yeah , really .
[ song playing ]
This is called " It Never Ends " .
[ singing along with song in Dutch ]
♪
And who is it ?
Trijntje Oosterhuis .
I think , this is how an angel sounds .
[ continues singing with song in Dutch ]
[ music stops ]
I really want to apologize for my behavior last night .
I 'm sorry I made you feel so uncomfortable .
No , it 's fine . Don 't worry about it .
You know , sometimes I have this thing , right here .
And it 's so powerful and wild .
And I like it . That 's the weird part .
I really like it . You understand ?
Yeah .
You do ?
Totally .
Normally , I just uh ...
just try to hold it down or ...
keep it in chains .
Why ?
[ sighs ] I don 't know why .
Too many rules , I guess ...
- It 's um ... - It 's what ?
It 's clau ... Yeah , I don 't know ,
It 's ... claustrophobic , you know ?
It 's like I become this person I don 't want to be .
Who is that person ?
I don 't know . It 's ... some guy .
Some normal guy who gets up in the morning and ...
[ sniffs ] ... takes his daughter to school and ... goes to work .
[ sniffling ]
Play a little squash once a week .
Have dinner with people I don 't even like .
And I 'm so tired of smiling all the time .
Come .
Come , I want to show you something .
[ birds chirping ]
[ Patrick screams ]
[ Bjørn screams ]
[ Patrick joins ]
[ both screaming and laughing ]
[ splash ]
- It 's fantastic . - This is the life , huh ?
[ both chuckle ]
[ kiss ]
Louise , thank you so much for helping out in the garden .
Oh , you 're very welcome .
[ Abel and Agnes giggling in background ]
Um , they want to show a dance .
Oh , that 's so nice . Maybe when we have coffee .
Agnes , can you set the table , please ?
Ah !
Patrick , maybe you could take a look at her finger ?
Sure .
[ speaking foreign language ]
It 's good that we have a doctor in the house .
I 'm not a doctor .
[ laughs ] But didn 't you say you were a doctor ?
Did I ? Oh , I lied .
- You lied ? - [ Patrick ] Yeah .
Sometimes I get a little insecure when I meet new people .
He just wanted to make a good impression .
[ speaking foreign language ]
[ Louise groans ]
What do you work with then ?
- I don 't work . - No ?
No , I 'm unemployed .
I 've never worked , I don 't believe in working .
[ speaking foreign language ]
Uh .
Oh , that 's wrong . It 's the other way around .
[ Karin speaks in foreign language to Agnes ]
[ Karin ] Okay ?
Sorry .
- [ Patrick ] Yes . - No , ow ! Okay .
Yeah , I got this , thank you .
Who needs a doctor , right ?
- [ Bjørn ] Yeah . - [ both chuckle ]
[ Patrick sighs ] Bread ? Yes .
You know , it 's a shame
that Holland is not really being recognized
as a producer of fine and high quality cheese
like Italy or France for example .
Oh , here . [ speaking foreign language ]
I mean , we are a cheese nation .
We export more cheese than any other country in the world ,
besides Germany , of course .
But I sometimes feel ...
that Dutch cheese is not getting the respect it deserves .
[ speaking in foreign language ]
Everyone should come with Bjørn and me to the market
and try some of Johan 's cheese .
Then they will give Dutch cheese the respect it deserves .
Johan said it himself .
Forget Stilton , forget Gorgonzola .
Dutch cheese , Dutch cheese is the number one , right ?
- Bjørn . - Hmm ?
The cheese at the market , it was good , right ?
- It was fantastic . - It was number one .
- [ Bjørn laughs ] - Johan said it himself , cheers !
- Cheers . - [ all clink glasses ]
[ speaking foreign language ]
Stop telling my daughter what to do .
It 's not up to you to tell my daughter what to do , okay ?
Okay , relax . I 'm sorry .
[ dance music plays ]
[ singing in foreign language ]
[ Patrick turns off music ]
[ speaks to Abel in foreign language ]
[ Patrick ] Sorry about that .
- [ Louise ] No , it 's okay . - [ Patrick ] Okay ?
One , two , three , four . [ starts music ]
- [ speaking foreign language ] - [ stops music ]
[ Patrick speaking foreign language ]
It 's okay . They 're both really good .
Yes , but he has no rhythm . And he 's messing up the routine .
No , but they are just kids .
Yes , but if he wants to reach his potential ,
he has to concentrate , right ? Right .
[ speaking foreign language ]
Okay , one more time . [ starts music ]
[ Patrick stops music , yells in foreign language at Abel ]
No , she has to stay because it 's a duet .
[ Louise ] No , she doesn 't want to .
[ Patrick ] No , she has to stay .
She doesn 't want to dance anymore .
[ Patrick speaking foreign language , starts music ]
[ throws and shatters cup , yells at Abel in foreign language ]
[ Patrick stops music and punches chair arms ]
[ Abel whimpering ]
[ Patrick speaking foreign language , starts music ]
[ Bjørn turns off music ]
Uh , what 's the problem ?
You cannot ... he 's only a child for Christ 's sake .
I mean , what the hell is wrong with you ? [ stammers ]
Can 't you see he 's crying ? He 's in pain ?
[ speaking foreign language ]
You can 't talk to him that way . What is wrong with you ?
Oh my god , what 's wrong ?
Because we do things differently ?
This is not about doing things differently .
It 's not about that .
No ! This is about doing what is right .
This is really ... to do what is right for you .
Like showing your son some love when he is crying
instead of shouting at him .
Yeah , and Patrick , what the fuck ?
Why can 't you just let him dance ?
Oh , that wasn 't dancing .
[ speaking in foreign language ]
Yeah , but you threw a cup at him !
[ speaking foreign language ]
Sorry , but I can 't listen to you talk to him that way .
[ speaking in foreign language ]
[ stammering ] You threw a cup at the wall !
Okay , stop this please . Please stop it .
[ footsteps , slams opens door ]
[ coughing ]
Bjørn , can you please take her inside ?
I don 't want her to see me like this .
[ breathing heavy ]
[ water running , brushing teeth ]
[ door opens ]
[ Patrick urinating ]
[ continues brushing teeth ]
[ Patrick flushes toilet ]
[ door shuts ]
[ Abel crying , Patrick talking in other room ]
[ Patrick speaking in foreign language ]
[ Abel moaning ]
[ Patrick yelling in foreign language ]
[ footsteps in the hall ]
[ Abel moaning ]
[ Patrick yelling in foreign language ]
[ Bjørn breathing heavy ]
[ television in background ]
[ eerie music ]
[ Bjørn shuts off television ]
[ water running ]
[ water running in sink ]
[ screen door slamming ]
[ footsteps ]
[ suspenseful music ]
[ stairs squeak ]
[ suspenseful music intensifies ]
[ door squeaks open ]
[ door shuts ]
- [ Bjørn ] Okay , let 's go . - [ car horn beeps ]
[ footsteps ]
[ car doors open ]
[ car door shuts , keys rattle ]
[ car starts , gas light chimes ]
[ puts car in gear and drives slowly ]
[ car rumbling ]
[ breathing heavy ]
[ truck approaching ]
[ truck passes ]
[ gas pump chiming ]
[ car rumbles by ]
[ car rumbling ]
[ eerie music ]
[ suspenseful music intensifies ]
[ speaking foreign language ]
[ car rattles and halts ]
[ starts car ]
[ tires spinning ]
[ breathing heavy ]
[ shuts car off ]
[ removes seat belt , opens door ]
[ shuts door ]
[ footsteps ]
[ suspenseful music ]
[ water splashing ]
Hello ?
[ knocks on door ]
[ screams ] Hello ! ?
[ footsteps , opens door ]
Louise ?
[ breathing heavy ]
Louise ! ?
[ yelling ] Agnes ! ?
[ footsteps ]
Louise ! ?
[ sobbing ]
[ hysterically ] Agnes !
[ breathing heavy ]
[ vehicle approaching ]
[ car rumbles to a halt , engine running ]
[ Patrick ] Hey Bjørn .
Thanks for the call .
I 'm glad you agreed to meet us up on the road .
Thanks for helping us out . It 's very nice of you .
Of course , hmm .
- [ footsteps ] - [ car engine running ]
[ breathing heavy ]
Get in the car .
[ whimpering ] Please don 't hurt us . Please don 't hurt my family .
We just want to go home .
[ whimpering ]
Hey , it 's okay . Relax .
As long as you do as we say , it 's gonna be fine .
[ whimpering ]
[ car rumbling ]
[ Louise ] Do you know when we will be back at the house ?
[ Karin ] It won 't be long now .
[ Louise speaking foreign language ]
[ Louise ] Is Abel alone at the house ?
No , Muhajid is looking after him .
He was up early anyway , so ...
[ car squeals to a stop ]
[ cranks emergency brake ]
[ keys rattle , engine stops ]
[ door opens and shuts ]
[ Patrick unzips pants ]
[ car radio in background ]
[ Patrick urinating ]
[ door opens ]
[ car rumbling ]
[ Louise ] Are we there soon ?
Be quiet .
[ Louise ] Excuse me ?
[ Karin ] Will you be quiet , please ?
[ suspenseful music ]
[ Louise ] Can you tell us when we 'll be back at the house ?
[ Karin ] Shhhhhh .
[ Bjørn ] We 're going to your house , right ?
[ car stops , cranks emergency brake ]
[ flashes headlights ]
[ car door opens ]
[ door shuts ]
Now you have to tell us what 's going on ...
Shut up . Shut the fuck up .
- Don 't talk to my family like ... - [ Patrick punches Bjørn ]
[ Agnes screams ]
[ Louise grabbing door handle ]
[ Bjørn groaning ]
[ speaking foreign language ]
[ Karin speaking foreign language ]
Louise , please let go of her .
[ Bjørn removes seat belt ]
- [ Patrick punches Bjørn ] - [ Bjørn grunts ]
[ Agnes screams ]
[ Karin slithers scissors from pocket ]
[ Karin ] Louise ...
[ Bjørn groaning ]
[ Karin ] You will let go , yes .
- No . - [ Karin ] You will , you will .
[ opens door ]
[ Agnes screaming ]
[ struggling , grunting ]
[ punching ]
[ Louise and Agnes screaming and gasping ]
[ hysterical shrieking ]
[ snip ]
[ door shuts ]
[ Louise screaming in foreign language ]
- [ car drives off ] - [ Louise screaming hysterically ]
[ somber music ]
[ car rumbles ]
[ brakes squeak , car stops ]
[ door opens ]
[ door shuts ]
[ whimpering ]
[ whimpering ] Why are you doing this ?
[ Patrick ] Because you let me .
[ Bjørn whimpers ]
Take off your clothes .
[ both whimpering , crying ]
[ thud ]
[ Louise grunts ]
[ somber music ]
[ singing haunting counterpoint melody in foreign language ]
[ haunting vocals continue ]
[ music ends ]
♪